Are you a social media addict?
你是一个社交媒体成瘾者吗？
Are you always checking your smartphone to see how many 'likes' you've received for your latest post?
你总是查看你的智能手机，看看你最新发布的帖子获得了多少个“赞”吗？
Maybe you feel comforted by the notification sound that someone has sent you a message?
也许你会因为有人给你发了一条消息的通知声音而感到舒畅？
Don't worry, you're not alone.
别担心，不只你一个人这样。
We check our phones an average of 150 times a day, and around 30% of the total time spent online is dedicated to social media.
我们平均每天查看手机150次，并且花在网上的总时间中，大约有30%都用于社交媒体。
Some experts now fear this habit could be damaging our mental health.
现在一些专家担心这种习惯可能会损害我们的心理健康。
This is something particularly afflicting young adults, according to a study from the University of Pittsburgh.
根据匹兹堡大学的一项研究，这是尤其困扰年轻人的一个问题。
It found the more they used social media, the more likely they are to be depressed.
研究发现，他们使用社交媒体越多，就越有可能抑郁。
In tests, those people who checked social media frequently were 2.7 times more likely to be depressed compared to those who spent most of their time generally surfing the internet, who had just 1.7 times the risk.
在测试中，那些频繁查看社交媒体的人患抑郁症的可能性是2.7倍，而那些大部分时间只是上网浏览的人患抑郁症的风险只有1.7倍。
The study found that exposure to "highly idealised representations of peers on social media elicits feelings of envy and the distorted belief that others lead happier, more successful lives."
研究发现，接触“社交媒体上同龄人高度理想化的生活引发了嫉妒之情，以及认为别人过着更幸福、更成功生活的扭曲信念”。
Some of us certainly feel sad when we're ignored on social media sites, or when we see someone else having a better time than us.
当我们在社交媒体网站上被忽视，或者当我们看到别人比我们过得更开心时，我们中的一些人肯定会感到难过。
But depression is a more serious condition and clinical psychologist, Abigail San, recently told the BBC that, "It's a real issue, and it's been getting significantly worse over the last 5-6 years.
但是抑郁症是一种更严重的状况，临床心理学家阿比盖尔·桑最近告诉英国广播公司说：“这是一个真正的问题，而且在过去的五六年里，情况明显变得更糟了。
You can get so hooked that it takes you away from your real relationships."
你可能会上瘾，以至于它让你远离了现实中的人际关系。”
However, Abigail does admit that social media is more likely to exacerbate pre-existing issues than directly cause them.
然而，阿比盖尔也承认，社交媒体更有可能加剧已经存在的问题，而不是直接导致这些问题。
Other research by Glasgow University found that teenagers are affected by the 24-hour demands of their social media accounts.
格拉斯哥大学的其他研究发现，青少年受到他们社交媒体账户全天候需求的影响。
It found that those with higher levels of emotional investment in social media, and who use it at night, were more likely to feel depressed and anxious.
研究发现，那些在社交媒体上投入更多情感，并且在晚上使用社交媒体的人，更有可能感到抑郁和焦虑。
Despite these warning signs, why do some of us continue to keep clicking?
尽管有这些警示信号，为什么我们中的一些人还继续不停地点击呢？
Well, I suppose we all want to be liked and we don't want to miss out on a conversation that's taking place online.
嗯，我想我们都希望被人喜欢，而且我们不想错过正在网上进行的对话。
But we need to know when to switch off our virtual online world and connect with the real world instead.
但是我们需要知道什么时候该关掉我们虚拟的网络世界，并与现实世界建立联系。